The skies, the thunderstorm
Stone carrying storms that cut to the bone
The serpent who teaches me not to
Inside me my goddess and my shield Scorpio's empire rising my destiny
after the show star shine is so bright watch the secrets unfold
I guess she asked me, she said I could go one-on-one.
That's fine, I don't mind going on with other people.
It's just, at that time, we really didn't need to talk one-on-one.
And it's like, no, she did bring Samman up,
and Samman is okay, but.
It was fine, but you know she's like but she didn't she didn't play like a little prank where she's like
Oh, oh, let me just read
I mean tell you a story about biscuits and then it was like about a man that was scared of this kids
And I don't know she this took the thumbnail as a man that was like putting ordering KFC and like
I don't know why he to order a piece of scared it, but anyway, then I said it's fine, but uh
It was by it's funny. We're not really sensitive anymore, right? Oh my god
I don't see how long that goes, but I do want to play the whole biscuit song because you wouldn't let me finish it
So you're gonna play the actual music video for the biscuit
Yeah
Crumble like a cookie when the heat's on stage beat a business biscuit still sitting in the cage talk tough online
But the flavor don't laugh
Snap like a cracker when the panel talks fast
Hook, beat us biscuits dry and blend
No butter, no jam, just dust in your hand
Claim you bring spice but you bring in regret
Panel got receipts, we ain't finished yet
You came to the kitchen but forgot the recipe
Your plate got nothing but re-hated fries. I'm the main course truth served hot. You're the snack that
But you're bringing regret panel got receipts. We finished yet you came to the kitchen
But forgot the recipe
Serving up crumbs while I feast on legacy fire in the oven you the smoke that won't stick
You don't don't rise cuz you're game too quick
Dry and bland no butter no jam. Just dust in your hand
Can you bring spice, but you bring in regret panel got receipts. We ain't finished yet
You're the snack that everyone already...
love for you is a bittersweet refrain a melody that echoes a heart in pain
though we may be apart you're always on my mind wishing you
in the silence i'll hold on to the past and cherish every moment that we're
I'll love you every day
Oh, yeah, we have to do something now. Did not be this saying that um
Well, she's saying that um, no, we had a good appearance with her
It was finally like we kind of like we're going to this talk normally
You know saying I was there and stuff, but what about what she said? She said uh
That oh remember that song like she said that I thought she had said at the other day
She's like well that I posted this I posted something on my community ball and that was about you
And I was like okay, and I was like okay, but then she's like when did I ever have a crush on you?
I think she did have a crush on me. Maybe like a little one at least a bunch of memory, but it's like big
It's not like oh how it always is. It's a good never like all our most
I don't know, but she liked me. I think she liked me for like, you know, one day maybe she was like, oh, you're cute. And she said, um, yeah, I think she said on her show, she's like, oh, we can like, you know, you can come over and we can just cuddle in the in the bed. I mean, she didn't, it wasn't like, it was like, she's not wanting to not say it, right? What? Oh, Jamie said no.
but she said it on the air and now she's saying I didn't say it anyway it was a great it was a weird
appearance but that was the song but she but anyway the song that she said was now she's saying it's
not about me well I have to replace my appearance like I need to see if she said it because um
oh okay so let me see
Yeah, but she did it about her ex-boyfriend or something now, but she said it was about me. No, I mean, I don't like to be called a liar, but
No, I actually don't want to play that though. I think that's gonna be up some more like the old
Me, I'm just gonna be alone right now. What do I look so like? Oh
In this case
Pretty exciting on the computer
Which are like
We were in the back again
Right at the Vatican guy that would meet it. Why does it look like the US Capitol look building almost exactly?
Well, I think it has a capital dome. I guess but
Do they have a pillar they have pillars too?
Didn't it look like the
Capital building am I right or I'm gonna screw
I can't put a little letter A, okay, let me see, what else do I want?
Do I need to make my face bigger? Okay, I put the link up, I pin the link, oh my god,
I already pin the link already. Oh, oh, guys, here, okay, good, here, let's see how this looks.
Greetings, my friend. When you came earlier and you just like, like, you said, oh, I'm watching
you and then you just left. And you don't- Who was I talking to though, when I said that?
I don't know. Was it me? Mason. Oh, Mason. Oh, you're trying to skin me. Mason was really
funny on Vita's show today, though, because he's like, hey, guys, hey, he's like, hi,
you know, he's like, I like your show a lot better. Psyche, because, you know, I think
there's weird things going on here. And he's like, these people are weird. I was like,
yep, you see it, Mason. And, uh, yeah. And then like, but then, you know, it's like
Trying to like lay in the mood. I just I wasn't trying to make him laugh and stuff like that and like, you know
I hope you it's like, you know, I came in late. I guess he threatened Sandman and stuff. Oh, yeah
She they he they got him to like because it's like and it but it's like they they knew you like they knew about it
Like that he did it to like, you know you or they they said and so they knew to like egg him on about it
And then he like yeah, but he just
Cracked so quick and he's like, yeah, I'm gonna get a weapon, you know
Yeah, he goes from like zero then he's mad and then he's like then he just wants to talk to me and it's like
You can't fuck with base. He's a gangster. Right. I know it's like I'm he's that's why you know
He's in my gang, you know, it's like because he's like
I mean it's like he's a little bit. I am unpredictable. No, we're your top dogs
Yeah, he's like, you know, he's really I'm a pretty good little person
Like, I feel like I'm a bad influence on maybe, you know, I don't know, I'm not the best.
But, you know, he thinks I'm one of the only nice people to him and that's kind of sad.
Like, I'm not even that nice.
You're the only nice person to him?
He's like he just wants to talk to me and stuff where he likes or just my show or I don't know like but you know
He's well you should go you should go everywhere and stuff
He just wants to ask questions. He went to summers and oh, I'm sorry. I have you block on you into summer
Is that look at how big I am?
No, you're into something my nose looks so big you went to summer
And he had a good time there, Summers, and that's good.
And Summers was nice to him, because yesterday,
when she came on, she was kind of giving him
a hard time a little bit.
And he was ignoring her, not trying to acknowledge him.
And then, but then he went to her show,
and he's like, you're pretty.
And she actually took it as a compliment.
Some people, some people.
As she should.
Why would anyone take that as a fucking negative?
Some people are going to compliment it.
They get fucking bent out of shape. Yeah
Look here little blades up here. You remember used to somebody being nice to them
Yeah, I know I know and see they can't take it
This is you run you remind me of like kind of like skipper and this guy reminds him Gilligan. Oh, I'm the skipper
What does that make this guy? Mrs. Howell Gilligan?
Apollo Apollo's Mrs. Howell
Yeah, are you Mrs. Howell or you're Gilligan? Hey, love me and I'll handle sighs
It's actually the professor from the human centipede. Oh, oh gross
Apollo welcome
And Paul is a joke. It's a joke. Oh, Paul. Who's who's noon you'll be about to noon
Hey guys, you know what you know, I really like I like if you type biscuits in the chat
But you put it in a five to ten dollars super chat or you don't hit up my cash app or okay
At least ten fuck the five dollars
If you want to do a reading tonight, yeah, too, I'll do like I'll do like three like good size readings
Really can but I'll just so I'll do free ones for the people my panel Apollo do one. Yeah
But uh, yeah, and then
What the fuck?
No, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Well, there you go.
Fuck it.
Don't be like that.
If you don't mind, I would just pull a card for me if you want.
I'll take two cards.
A couple cards?
OK.
Yeah, I need a reset from the last reading you gave me.
Nothing happened, but I was worried all week.
You're worried?
You shouldn't worry about the cards, though, you know?
What was the hangman?
The hangman always worries me.
Yeah
You know you never know when the shoe is gonna drop. Oh my god. Yeah, the other shoe
I don't mean on the first shoe drop that it's I'm not sure they just have a broken socks
Let's take away from all windows
Yeah, please. Yeah, especially windows. You have the you have the tower the wall
Yeah, tower come crashing down
Well, I had it
No, he had it fall out of the tower. Oh, no
Well, I've had these legs. Yeah, I just had these haters exposed cards. So he's not traditional cards
I just gonna pull
Yes, you can see at least you can at least see the good stuff like you get a
Exciting army. I love haters. Okay, so some of me to stop stop stop shut feeling okay. I'm gonna shut playing someone keep going keep going
Keep going
Stop
Oh my gosh, okay, so a few cards like popped out, okay
Okay, okay, so we have it says eight tweets or zero petty birds tweet
Whoo, that's the Emma Leviathan, okay, be issue mad at you
I hope so you hope so. Oh my god. I love when they're angry. Yeah, okay
There he is. We got you. We got we got envious of your career and the money you make. Oh, yeah, I know they are
Yeah, so I think
Well, I don't know. I'm about to start a donation. They wish they had my money. I worry about psyche
No matter what you do or say everything turns great
So what?
You ever heard that song before like you ever heard that song before he's saying that's the Goo Goo dolls
I don't like that psyche everything you do or say up not says
Or you matter what you do or say everything turns gray
Are you making fun of me who said that I'm not this I'm not I'm not like I'm gonna tell you about a song
Were you reading it for me? Why would you say that to me?
No, there's a song that says that so I saw of all the lines and all the songs
I mean, there's a billion songs right a million a trillion lines. You could pick. Why did you exactly?
Positive song pick a positive song, you know, you are the light you are the
What was my second card I forgot? Oh your second card. I'm sorry. It was I'm their empties of your
Oh my money my money and my wealth. Yes, you might know this person, right?
Yeah, that looks like somebody I know
God, is he reading the aterocards? Yeah, he's doing a reading this one set and the third card says theater is fresh
Woodsy smell cleanse a new home of its old energies and unwanted spirits while
unwitting well unenviting
Well, sorry, well inviting fresh energetic vibes and protecting. Oh, I love a good woodsy smell. I love that
I love that so my dad used to like have like this
You know has cabinets with it's not like that. So it all looks like pine. Yeah, like pine saw. Yes, he's cool
He's cedar. Yeah, like a cedar chips and stuff. Oh, yeah
But yeah, and so but it's also like this person also looks maybe like some kind of like, you know, spying maybe or something
So I know that girl
You know her. What's your name? Yeah. Yeah, Cindy Cindy Cindy Lou who okay?
So you know your cards with some hater cards Mesa. Thank you. Thank you psych. You're welcome
Goddy
what
Hey Gotti, what happened man? Like you were you were that this guy was getting in it with you like it stuff like that just a while ago
Well, you saw how angry he was because he had a man for a wife. You saw that yeah, but God he you have a guy
He's like it went on it went on for too long though. Gotty like whatever would happen
Well, you know all those people are
But God, he wasn't really frustrating you that much though that you had to deal with it. No
Yo, what's up, Frankie?
What's up, Jason?
What's up, baby?
J-Dog, is that you?
Yo, what's up?
J-Dog.
What's up?
Can't see you, man.
What's going on?
J-Dog, show me like you.
J-Dog, let's see.
The what?
They said, show me you, and then they do not moon the show.
Yeah, you don't want to see that.
Don't show the moon.
Don't show the hole.
It was a full moon the other night.
Full moon.
Show me you don't full moon.
You really did that, dude?
Yeah.
You have no shame, huh?
You see me right this is me. Yeah, I can see you dude. What are you doing? You're in the dark
Yeah, just like Jake Dawson's dark
Well, they say all that dirt will come into the light
Jay dog, you're in the dark just like I'm in a dark. So it's okay to be in dark, right?
Floating are you in the same room? Are you doing the same room? Maybe no, we're not in the same room
They're the same closet to say in the same bed. No, no, we're not in the same bed. I'm the same
You got the cat eyes
Dude psyche that was fucked up earlier, man
They it was supposed to just be you and beat are talking and then all of a sudden Sam
I want to bring his goofy ass up in there Christ to fuck it all up
Go figure
Sam and well he was called that he was got all the n words and then I said you're not even black
There's so many in the chat or something like that is like unexplained freak accident.
J-Doug, we can't help that the sun goes down and everything turns all dark.
Mason, it's like he's doing a reading, man.
I was trying to do it.
Oh, gosh.
I don't know.
It's kind of like the jigsaw deck.
Who's this for?
This is for like everybody, baby
It says you cut them off and they're still watching. I don't know
Okay, what else we got?
Hey, we have this devil harm person that says someone is doing black magic or juju on you. Oh, you know that is
They will come kind of manipulation
And uh, unintentional, they don't realize they're sending you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes they will send you words and sometimes people will do unintentionally, sometimes people will do
Yeah, they beat up and kill people. Yeah, what?
I want to talk about oh John and Gacy you're talking about I mean that's the only one I mean most of them don't do that
Well, what about terrifying?
What about your friend the torture clown, you know, he doesn't beat up people
I don't know how am I supposed to know that he promotes love and
Creepy clown guy the one who's like
Yeah, yeah, he pulls all this corkscrew out of his nose and he licks it
He's weird
Oh, you show your fucking asshole to everybody, but he's real.
No, I didn't show my asshole, nobody.
No, I didn't show my asshole.
My asshole didn't get it.
All right, dude.
He's the weird one.
And you know what?
Me?
Who's dodgy?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Say it again.
I couldn't hear you.
He didn't say any of your but- your but will follow.
She sent it?
Yeah, she sent it.
I
Whose dog is that the first it's cause the negative is a fire sign. I don't know
That's Panda
Scary rabbit Jesus the poet show man directing towards you instead of
Coming here directly, okay
That's Mason
So like you what is that what is that?
It's a bad bunny
I think the candle rabbit, you know what it's awesome
What are you doing, man? What's up? What's up?
What's up, Mason?
With the dogs dogs barking. Oh my god. Yeah, the dogs are howling outside man. They're howling
I have the windows open right now to the one to the room and the dogs are how he's wasted do you can hear it?
This is because
Y'all seem really dry like look who loves yeah, bye. Bye. Bye. Bye. Good. Hey
I wanted them to leave one of me low with Mason and Apollo
Apollo watch this. Okay. Just sit in that corner like a good boy
I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. Oh, no, no, leave. Oh, he didn't leave. Okay. Good
Well, I like you. Yeah, you want to go out either you want to go out either leave or J dog because what were they doing?
Well weren't they doing is the question what weren't they doing?
Um
Apollo you there
It's like I don't think what was there
Get out of here
Welcome welcome to the circus that escaped asylum
Where tarot cards fly, and trolls get tried
You in the panel verse, baby
My father's psych, the cat daddy
Psych in the building, cards on deck
Tarot spread wild like a hacker on the net
Got linoa in the corner, claws out for lies
Tricks plodding chaos with those cosmic eyes
Mubbles in the mix, we don't play fair
Chat blowin' up like divine confessions
True bombs drop, no time for confessions
You on logic, we bandit
Drama, we mend it
Panel full of chaos, but the vibes transcendin'
If a troll wanna bark, we clap back politely
With Andromalleus, watchin' nightly
Welcome to Psych Awakens TV
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre, believe me
We laugh, we scream, we read the unseen
Prophecy and cosmic mistakes, Alyssa in the chat, she a mystery queen
DJ Electric got the beat so clean,
Beater with the panther, strength divine She teams chaos with the stare and the line
We don't do fake, this trap's too real We roast you kindly, but the love's the deal
Got minds with swords, keeping gates tight They swing truth like justice in the moon, like
Gifted subs, yeah the coke keeps growing Community wild, but the energy's flowing
Welcome to Psyche Awakens TV
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre
Believe me, we laugh, we scream
We read the unseen
Father Psyche, the cat daddy
King of the stream
Welcome to Psyche Awakens TV
We're Truth and Madness
If the same T, it's a family affair
It's dysfunction supreme
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Cards flip, candles drip, shadows in the mist
Trolls talk slick, but they cease to exist
We're half chaos, half oracle flame
And every night's a ritual in Psyche's name
No scripts, no filters, no chill in Psyche
We stream raw truth to the morning light
So grab your tea, grab your mic and vibe
We the strangest fam that's still alive
So pull up a chair the rituals be gone. It's like a weekend TV with a crazy one
This ain't YouTube
This is a underworlds talk show
Hey summer you are now initiating
This is a good
That's actually good. And so is this
It's new in a few minutes. Hold on. Give me a few minutes Mason. Watch this one. Just tell me what you like, okay?
Tell me if you like this
Airplane mode, I felt it in my skin
So I was sitting like designer gold
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing
Not to be solicial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you crave the chaos I fed
Cause love like alls ain't never dead
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I want to curse you
I could never run away
We trade halos for horns, it's fair
Every wound you gave, I wear
We take turns being the villains' muse
But damn it, I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial
But you made my pain perpetual
So I did something sexual
Just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from the strangers layer
Just to prove that I still care
You'd fall apart cause you know it's true
No one sends a way out
not to be divine but i love you even when i want to cause you i could never
I can't forget what was never spoken
Every scar, a holy mark
Every kiss, another spark
Not to be divine, but I love it
Did I get, what do you think?
Maison.
The Rihanna?
Yes, I have her logged in my basement
and she performs music for me.
I'm just kidding.
That's not very fun.
Well, actually, I haven't, I'm not, I'm not funny enough.
So I can.
Yeah, but oh, there you are.
Hey Maison.
Yes, I see it.
What did it mean to remember?
Remember when I asked you you and you kidnapped Rihanna for me and then she came in we forced her to do a
Recorded concert and she did a whole album. I don't remember. When was that remember that? That was last week
So I key who is what would tell me get so I don't mind for it. It's not important
So like it's not important. No, no, what is it?
No, it's not Rihanna. It's my own song. I mean it's like it's not a person. It's like the person doesn't you're just playing a song
I was but it's you know, they there's not like our actual vocalists
It's like an amalgamation of many people's voices. I don't think if I don't know some of them. I don't know
It's just so it's like you remember how crazy it was earlier when I was over at
Beat us channel with you on there and stuff like that a guy see a man was making me mad. I know my gosh
Remember you used to meet another thread. They told you you can't they'd be threatening
Yeah, so I can be the says that would get her channel or something take you down if I do that
But no, but psyche I made it up to her though
That's another video
ë±
I didn't hear you. So that video is made for somebody like that, you know, like in the panel verse, the panel verse. Yeah, the panel verse. Yeah, panel. How do you know about the panel verse? Who told you about that?
You told me about it. So I can you told me that there's people that go to the panel verse. Did you play that for her?
Her like thing wasn't working or something. That's a great song. She'll love that
Well, I don't know I mean
But I posted I posted stuff on her discord and she doesn't like really I don't think people check the discourse anymore
I think um, you know what? I think that um, Kate the guy KZ like I think
Like she thinks I'm a weirdo now because like all these people in the chat were saying I'm just like a weirdo and stuff
And so I don't think she like really and but um, I think you know, it's not really I think she says I'm tonight
I think but I
I don't know it's like I got a good friend in the lower chat. I want to introduce you to him
His name is Hitesh Tomar
Okay, he's from India. He might come up on the panel. He's a funny guy
This guy's fucking funny man. If he comes up here, just you know, treat him right if you don't mind
You know, he's fucking right, but don't don't don't get turned off. If he says a friend of mine, you know
Last few people that you brought on like I like to put screwdrivers. No, but this guy this guy's serious
This guy's fucking funny man. Now when I'm telling you this funny, you know, you know
I like to fucking laugh at funny things. This guy's fucking fun
Soon as he opens his mouth, you'll be on the fucking floor. You'll be on the floor laughing. I'm gonna like him
Right right off the bat. You're gonna love this guy. I don't think so. Hit-tatch Tomar. He's from India
I don't like I don't like his name. I don't like I don't know what he's like
I just you don't like his name. I don't like his name. I love the Indian people. I do love the Indian people. Oh
In my ears
It's funny man. I'm gonna get off camera. This is a brand new camera and so I'm not used to
I'm just gonna I'm just gonna like it's a little fuzzy. Yeah, I know. I'm just gonna turn it off
I'm going blind. Actually
What what did you think about that song you said you liked it. Yeah, I love that song. That's one of my favorite songs
When I die I want them to play that my funeral I'm gonna play that your funeral gaudy. I hope so
Well, I'm planning it right now the Indian people love you
Please, they're calling like Kali Ma on me, but I know Kali Ma.
You betrayed Shiva. You betrayed Shiva. Kali Ma is coming for you.
You're calling your Kali is Shiva, Shiva is Kali.
You don't know anything about it. Got it. Got it. I love it. You know, all right. Tell me the name of the one with the elephant face
What's the name of that one? Yes. Yes. I know I know all about that stuff
My good friend Hitesh Tomar told me all about that stuff
Well, just because you know one Indian person doesn't mean very much. If you know one, you know them all billion strong
Dottie yo always small said God he wouldn't he die. That's what always smiles said
When I die, I don't think God can die people. I don't know what you're thinking
Well, well, why would you tell me that though? Goddy always smiles told you that I'm sorry
I'm gonna die. I want to die of starvation starvation from
Um, from like having no one donating at all
For like a month long period
Indians are not allowed here. Oh see that he doesn't feel welcome now hit that come on up, dude
Let Indians go away. I'm just kidding. Talk to him for five minutes. He'll follow
My sister
I just feel like oh god. I want to introduce me to an Indian
You know the next day. I know he's a dot
He's a dart indeed, not a feather.
I know, well that's, yeah.
Okay, I'll have, okay, in that case, I'll have him on.
All right, yeah, come on up, Attesh, come on up.
Tell him hello.
You don't have to stay long if you don't want, two minutes.
Yeah, I know, I'm so rude, aren't I so rude
and like then people like don't want to even like talk to me?
No, you're not rude, dude, you're just drunk.
I'm not even that drunk, I'm not even that drunk.
I just have almost one of these
and I have one other one to drink, I don't even drink it.
Because I'm drunk.
Matt Mason said he said so the song
But yeah, that was just like, you know, I would say you know, we have we have
The certain uses right like and they're like maybe like these archetypes
I don't know at least it kind of reminds me of my mom a little bit
She was beating up that guy in the car man. That was funny shit
What
Where did you find it first?
Are you going to water mason? Are you okay? It sounds like you're you're caught you're under the sea
So I think you know it's it sounds it's very very bad
So I can what does it sound like you can't never think you're snorkeling
And you're talking through like that fucking work every time he says I'm at work. I'm laughing my ass off
You know, he says he's at work. He's in his bedroom, right? He's sitting on the bed
He has a laptop on his fucking
No, I'm talking about Hitesh the Indian he's on he's on a call center, right? He's doing a call center job
So he says he can't come up. He's so busy. Oh
Please
Yeah, uh
Yes, you sound like you're drowning
Backwards is like some kind of like
Rome raw motte Rome motte remote like remote
Backwards Scotty my words are called backwards remote Mason. You sound like you're going backwards. Yeah, and look at the lol
Like that's backwards and forwards that that it's the same words. Wow pay Google play. Oh my god Google play cards
I don't yeah, can you send me like
You want to send me one? I'll yeah, I accept I accept any donations. You want to sell I can you know, maybe by a
Backwards behavior 100 what?
Oh, you didn't eat today, huh? You didn't eat anything. I didn't eat today
I didn't you know, but I could I have like a lot of I actually this monopoly game on McDonald's has is so amazing
Oh, yeah, you want some prizes? Yeah. Yeah, well
Well, one of the things was like I'm almost like 10,000 points. And so that's like several I can have several copies this week
several
Like a bunch of that. Yeah, so
It's just like my my cards are all messed up right now. I should they have
Credit I just like PayPal credit is a big weird. It's a weird thing. Oh, here we go. Yes, I'm gonna
Oh, it's great Mason's back. Thank God come again. Oh finally Mason
Hey, God, he can you hear it better now? Yeah, who's that fake Mason? It's above me
God, what do you see another one?
Yeah, there's a drum kid and then there's you
Yeah, that's me like right there guy. That's me. How do you do that? No kids here. Yeah, I have two of me
There's two of me right over you. Oh
One of you is enough Mason. I can't handle
It's like I think actually you'd love two of them right now. I don't
Want this one right here
By Diana
Let me see. Hold on. Uh-oh. Gaudi, I was drowning before. Gaudi, I had to get out of drowning.
That's my new sound effect. Do you like it? What is it? You. That's your voice. Getting
kicked in the balls. My God. My God. My God. Fall down the stairs.
That sounds like a polo fall out the window
I know right
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Thank you
Gaudi, I was supposed to go to my own conclusions, man.
Uh-oh.
Mason are after you again.
Gaudi, they're after me again. You're right, Gaudi. You gotta be careful.
What conclusions have you come to?
Mason, yeah, what's conclusion? I have a good book. That's what Daryl told me. So that got him
Daryl
Yeah, Daryl. What do you say?
He said it comes to your own conclusion. Oh
Joni said something about a re reading
I think she's ready to donate um what's up no well it's again nobody wants to be a
member anymore and it's like what does that mean so I can't let me come to your own
I don't really worry too much about what the audience says because they don't support me anymore really so it's like, you know, I can do what I want and I will put up what it's like put up one of those goals like put two of those goals up.
You want to get to 20 bucks.
I want to get to, I'd like to get to $5 you know really but.
Oh I love this song.
Rest in peace, Tara Johnson.
WWE? No, I don't. I used to. It's crap now.
Gotty. What? So you're not really into wrestling? I used to be, man.
There's not much to watch
But we friends, forever, my friend.
Besties.
Yeah.
Cameras glitch and chat on fire mods begging me to cut the wire, but not I like my circus
I love this mess every trolls just a test stop and mess got you rude absurd and free
But we friends forever my friend you got a year's friend forever, man
I'd spend my chat then held it down
You got layers like a deep dish slice
under all that shade a
Heart made of ice and maybe rice so let's light that cigar raise the mic another night a chaos
brought the drama the heat the fun and weirdly it feels like you're the one i'm not the one
though yeah you crazy but your family now rolling through fire still taking a bow no matter the
madness no matter the weather we can't control but we stick together love you got it that's
I think it is, Mason. You're right.
Greatest song you'll ever hear. Thank you, Psych.
Mason, you got a song? I don't have one. Oh, man, I'm sorry.
Got it. There's not one for me. I mean that I have maybe soon
Who knows like you I mean oh god. Yeah, that's the wrong thing
So I know what you meant. I meant to say you're Dave. Go honey. I didn't mean oh
You got to pay $10 you'll get a song he says
That's who said that it's like you wrote $10 you get three songs
Biscuit bitches
You came to the kitchen, but for God, we're not finished yet
Crumbs while I feast on legacy on the fire in the oven. You just started your dough. Don't rise cuz you're game too quick
Be this bitch gets dry and bland. No butter. No jam. Just dusting your hand claim. You bring spice
But you bring in regret panel got receipts. We ain't finished
I'm the main course, truth served hot
You're the snack that everyone already forgot
Beat us biscuits left on the shelf
Try to serve shade but you played yourself
Panel lights on truth sharp like a knife
Biscuits crumble, welcome to real life
That's the meanest picture I've ever seen what this talk was on me God
Yeah thing that is
That was nice
That's the first one of two
We need one more
Then we can shut the panel down
What's wrong with you you sick what you sick
Me yeah, go drink something man
Wait, wait, how do you know if I'm sick though got some God
Well psyches in his feet of stars and stripes parade
Fish tacos on the table
Another wild charade
He's hitting on the straight men
Come on, lose that shirt
Meanwhile, Vita's on the hotline
Yelling till it hurts
Pretty pages dodging simps
Like dodgeball in the gym
Canada dry got gonged off
Didn't even swim
Summer spunky Marseille flashing
Chaos on the feet
And here comes a porn bomb
Oh Lord
fuzzy bear arthur's stirring pots like he's cooking up a scare truckerado
rumbles in salmon's chasing views dj electro's cartoon face is breaking all
the rules
We've gone too far, we've turned the trolls into our own memes.
Welcome to the show
Where every wild night
Becomes another in-joke
In Kentucky where the bluegrass sways
Lives a maiden whose tattoos tell her days
Hair flows free like a river bend
Sweet summer, dick or sun, everybody's friend
Let her love shine through
There is him softly like the night hold stars
Tattooed maiden with fire in her skin
Every battle she faced she rose again
Sweet summer, fierce and bright
Kentucky woman with a lion's fight
She'll yell at me, but she'll make me smile
Sweet summer walks with grace every mile
Tattooed maiden with fire in her skin
Every battle she faced
She rose again
That's a beautiful song.
Let's hear the Joni song.
Dottie.
What?
What song do you have for, what song do you have?
Jimmy Crack corn.
So that's supposed to be funny psyche. I was supposed to laugh or no
Jimmy crack corn
Yeah
You know it
No, what is that so I can never heard of?
Well, you keep calling me psyche. I make God eat. Thank you
I meant to say God
You give your heart away, open-handed and free
They took cheap shots where they couldn't see
You got the raw deal, they call you a mystery
I know you've heard it all before, so I don't shout it anymore
How many times I feel that strange ache inside?
But I stood alone
Every scar a secret carved in stone
Carrying stones that
Actually did it fuck. Hi. I
Didn't know how to do it
Have you done it before no no? And I don't even know what that big J is. Oh, oh, that's a
That's you. I know it is the avatar. You put it is the editing profile picture
No, I don't know. I didn't want to I mean, it's like I'm laying on my bed and it's dark in here like
and
I wasn't planning, but she got me all riled up.
I'm sorry. You know...
It was just it's always the timing every time I come in
Every time I come in it's something right
Every time it's like so much like it's like a sword fight or a gun fight or like a throwdown
Or like a pizza fight or like a cartwheel or like laughter
And or at least
Yeah, they really put a pin your pin down the show like really if you've tried it, but it's like yeah, it's very
Are you good like are you okay? I think I you know, I love you and it's like I know what I do songs like every day
You know, but it then it's like, you know, like love songs about you and so I can I can do those, but uh
We'll have a weird so I you know, I bet you know, I was trying to do it different like little things that um
Like they have like I have like these sample her music, whatever, but
Yeah, I just think it's timing to be quite frank with you from from
Not to get into that but what I what I mean and this is just my story at this point from a distance looking I
just think
I know I feel like I mean, you know like you know just like today like it was a weird day because like beta and I like
I don't know if you saw that but I was like, you know
I'm actually your show like she was like saying when I was like I was doing my show today
And she's like so like a couple people who came in and said oh well beta said
To come on and like she'll do one-on-one talk with you
Yeah, okay. Well, this is like an ambush. This is gonna be something. There's like something that's gonna be embarrassing or
Again, you know, it's like kind of like set up just so they're buried
But I was like, I'll do it anyway
And so I went and it was it was like when I won with her for a little bit and it's like and then we kind of like
You know, she's like she started asking me about why was I so like
You know
You know triggered by the biscuit or whatever, right? And she hit the AI art of me like freaking out holding KFC
Was it that that was never that's never happened, you know
Well, that's it was like, you know, I mean, it's you know, I don't I mean in a rap
But it's just like an ongoing right a little thing that I don't know. It's like
I don't think you're participating as well. It sounds like right. Yeah, but I think we made a lot of really good progress though
Like I was like, well, okay
So if we're not friends anymore
We're like, you know, then I can just be we can be content creators and like, you know, kind of like just play around and like because
Wait, wait, you know, it's you know, you know, I'm a pretty impressionable like empathic first, you know
The visual I just saw when you said that
You're like a like what do you call those like the like a conge like a two children like they're glued together
You know a conjuring
Yes
We're no longer friends, but I see like unless there's a surgery. There's something really attached there
I don't know if it's just a tailbone an arm
Share I was trying to like share like
Like you know I did like
you know at one time I was trying to like you know share with her and they say
you know kind of like give a friendly thing so I tried to make some I mean a few AI photos
you know and it's like you know and she you know we know she does not like AI at all
she's had a bad
So I hope tonight they did a kind of redeem the reputation from her like you know her hate of AI
And so let me see if I don't but where's my I used to have these pictures of her
I think it might be my gallery. Well like when you're a little did anyone ever say no to you and you actually like no
No means no and then you stop and you put it down or you walk away
Well, it's like, no, isn't that kind of like a human thing where it's like,
I don't know. Yeah. I mean, no, it's like when, especially like when people here know that they
would, it's like a curiosity that's like somebody saying, you can't, you know, you can't do this.
You can't eat this. You can't drink this. You can't, you're forbidden. Oh, you can't say this.
And, and of course we all want to like speak around and
You know do it except when you're a kid, you know, you might have a parent like, you know
That'll catch you or ground you or and then you get older. It's like, no, there's nobody's there except your own fucking mind
I can't see I don't know. I'm not seeing anything I'm putting up on the screen. Let me see. Maybe it's because I don't know what I did
No, I know it was me is me
I'm trying to figure out if I can put up. I can't see anything. I don't know what I'm doing. I'm on my cell phone
So I can't even see the cat. I have no clue. Oh
Who's this back? I mean, I have to take some things. Okay. I see I just have like a million things on stage right there
But I yeah, okay. I was also I don't know. I've been playing with these sayings forever
I I paid for like so many months in a row that it's like
I really want to write a book or something eventually with my story that I've been through, especially this last year, like 8 to 9 months, but.
This thing with trolling I have so many fakes
It's just like I have no idea why people are wanting to wear my skin all day every day on I like
I've turned like two or three different streams and like there
I am like not some are exactly my name and some are just parts of my name and then I'll they just like everywhere
Are you a troll?
Well, don't be sexy with that voice, you know.
That's not sexy, that's not a sexy voice.
Are you a troll? I'm just asking you a question.
I'm not a troll, I'm real. I'm the real Joni Bologna.
I'm, there's only one in your-
Joni Bologna.
There's so many.
Scotty, that sounds like a mafia name, huh?
Yeah, it does.
I know it, I know it's Jimmy Salami.
Joni the tongue.
I should see an, I should see a mafia woman.
My god, what's the deal, Joanie? I have no the fuck clue why I sent them all on fire
I can't make it stop. I mean, I'm like being terrorized, dude
I mean like I like what I'm one stream tonight
It's like I just kind of peeked in and wasn't gonna say anything and I saw I saw four of me. Oh
That's King of Pines
with king of pines and then buddy the buddy one and uh
the tan the tan is as good because i got one so they'll knock them over the head and drag
their dead carcass aside so tell tell me real quick what's the story with those three i
oh i don't have so much drama it's ridiculous it's it's grown it so that's all it is it's three
dudes it's all it's all it
Well I don't know the okay so like the one is a fallout from the elisa all the people that
are rejected or turned away that how that all blossoms you know there's always been a community
of people that apparently have had such relationships where it's just you know it's
I never understood it some go back 10 years right I've only been there once and I could tell that all three of them
Oh my god, knowing each other once, you know for a while. They've known each other now
They came in like like sliding in the home plate that day. It's like I saw you I was like, oh my right
Yeah, I don't know you said a few words and in the room like quieted. It was funny
well i am god you know i don't agree i there's some things i know about you i don't agree
but you do you do have a something about you there is a part of you i'm you know pulled to
like i'm not like just like like there's something about you more than what you say i think
Even though I'm looking at an avatar now, we barely know each other right John. I never paid you to say this
You see that everybody almost a complete stranger and she's giving me a full testimonial
Yeah, you gotta do a little bit
You got a little touch of this and it's like like if I was making a cocktail or something right or something on the stove
I'm gonna add a sprinkle of this a little of that
I'm gonna add a you know my own like if I was making a Bloody Mary everybody
There's a different way to make it so I could
Little bitters if I wanted bitters, do I want celery? Do you want olives? You want do you?
What what else you want pepper?
You want good vodka? You want shitty vodka?
So if I'm gonna if I'm gonna take over any three of those three
New streams that I'm going to yeah, I figure which one's the best one to hit
Well, it just depends. I'm not sure like I gotta know more about you and what I'm asking I'm asking your opinion
Which one's the best one?
Do you want more of a smoother community, or do you want more of an argumentative back-to-back?
I like a mix. I like a good mix.
There's a lot of fallout right now.
What is that?
What the fuck?
You dropped the phone?
What is that?
Oh, that's his thing. His rug.
Oh, I'm trying to play with it.
The rug is like
I thought that was like a porno thing those sparkles what you didn't make assumptions
Why did no, I don't know. I'm not like you. I'm not around like I'm not like a
You hear Lola? Hold on here. Do you hear Lola?
Oh look, help me Lola.
The magic carpet.
Oh yeah, they turn off the air hole,
and you turn off the air.
See that, yeah, she's in that beautiful rug.
That is like, it's probably like,
it's made of, it's basically made of wetsuit material.
You know, it's about-
Dim sum cellarim.
There you go.
It's made out of nice little magic.
Why are there spark, why are there little sparkles?
It's magic.
I got it, yeah, it's Hollywood magic right there.
Oh, now we're in the bag. I mean, I like it. It was okay, but there you go. I'm trying to show you what what is that?
What is it? What are you leaving my floor there? Oh my god, is that a gift? Is it a mouse?
Hopefully it's a mouse. Oh my god, and I can't eat a mouse the other day
I think I chased him around and then he drop it and then it would start kind of running around and then it hid for like two days
Meow
Oh
It's very traumatizing.
You should just let him like, hello.
No, he left it there.
He's like, wait.
That's for later.
Hello, I'm looking at you.
Wait, you guys make you put on my pictures?
Where?
What?
Me and Bita on the screen.
Is that Bita?
I'm looking at her, the carcass of the mask.
Wow, she looks great.
I think she does like that there.
I think he has, I feel like I just have a picture.
I have never seen her like in a clear light ever.
Just, it's always been kind of like,
it feels like there's like, really like, yeah.
I don't want to say filter, but yeah, I don't know. I never really saw her clearly, but look
That was that I thought that was her I was like that I nailed it. I saw I nailed it there. No, it's my sense
No, it's like Joan Baez. Oh
Well, that's personally on mine. So cats don't really eat mice. They just catch them and kill them
Wait a minute
Are you just gonna leave it on the ground for this fake Johnny? It's a fake mouse. It's okay. Are you promise? I couldn't see yeah, it was fake
No, well, but put him outside or something. I mean, you know, he's gonna send it to be the I'm gonna take it away from a cat
Is he's really dead I listened
Do I call you Goddy or God it come on
To call you God. I prefer God on
There's there one are you
I bowed I turn my back no no no no no no you don't have to do all that just
what i'm busy taking them off the
cross that i put them back on the
cross one one sorry something like
one like facts about yourself or
something they give you and give me
your astrological sign i still need
that and then i want to like make your
song right now and but go ahead and i'll
shut up i'm gonna shut up i'm so sorry
joining talk to god he's a good person
to talk to i'm like
Why is this picture of you and this lady in the middle with the you're showing all your teeth your grill as they say
There
That's a sweetie pie. I know
Oh, what a crazy man a man that likes men, but that loves beautiful women. Oh look, it's Darth Daryl
Who's that smile that was the fucking goal right there
Is it is that the Daryl guy with the screen name? That's the other guy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah my own little mind
He's alright. He's alright. He trips out sometimes, but he's a good
What about the one guy so he's psyche psyche can I ask a question psyche?
I'm gonna ask him too. Are these clean underwear? Do I need to wear underwear?
But he's like sinister in a way not sure I can't pick it up yet. I don't know everybody's sinister here. I know right
Like a coven
Just so you know that pine thing he was growling the other day. Did you see that? No, no
I haven't watched them enough to really get the gist of these people but uh 15 years
I think I think I'm liking buddy's style
There's a bunch of there's a bunch of me's on and they were pretty mean-spirited
But he buddy their style I seem to
Nice on the tan the tan thingy, but wow look who's here who?
Holy shit royalty, who's royalty? I'm
Mr. Tomar welcome
How are you mr. Gotti? I'm great pal. How you been man? It's been a long time two years
Been in hibernation
Yeah, me and him a we had a falling out two years ago. He held a grudge and this is the first time we're back on panel together
Are you gonna sell it? No, then won't sell it like man. No, no, it's over
Is this the ink is he from England? No, no, it's not finished on Spanish
What was the following out about?
something about
Yeah, we don't remember what it was remember. Yeah, it's not even
So we don't we don't hold grudges. Yeah
There's over a woman
Okay
Blonde
With psyche I want psyche to meet your man with psyche. What are you dude?
He always does this he's fucking rude to the the guest that bring up here. He's done
This is the third time now. He's done this to a guest that I welcome to his channel
Can I ask you a question? No recommendations, huh?
Mm-hmm
Recommending people society
Mike had found a little those little field mice right and after a while it didn't move
So, you know, they pick it up and they drop it it runs away
So I figure I got to save the little mouse, you know, I let him have fun, right? He doesn't eat it
But his teeth are sharp.
So I took it like I got it and I took him outside
his body was still warm and I did like,
what do you call it, not mouth to mouth,
but I did like a panel on his chest and I prayed.
Here come angels and guys.
He came back, right?
If you can make him rise up, I will believe.
His eyes were wide open and I didn't get a blink
or nothing, it didn't work.
Oh, shit.
So you just have to throw it across the street then.
I didn't throw it, I laid it down in case
What I said it was a poor rodent's lifeline we all die one day
That's why they have like 20 kids when they like your birth
Yeah, but don't they have a little soul. I'm not sure
No, yes, they do
It's a collective thing
Yeah
But you shouldn't go out actively killing them no
What only they become a past you pray flush it down the toilet no no no
No, I saw one of those little, you know those shorts, you know on tic-tac or the other one
And like the little cat came up and the lady was boiling water and she was looking the other way
And he just dropped it in the water. I mean it was like horrible my eyes
I'm like I wasn't ready for it, but I don't know I don't know if it was dead or not
He dropped it and then he had a fake third finger went up like a cat finger and I'm like what I
Mean, yeah, it was like what the hell
So, Joanie, all three of those guys, they don't do panels like this, they only do call-in shows?
No, nobody does panel, no, they do...
They do the phone number.
They do the phone number, yeah, they do the phone number.
All three of them.
Yeah, all three of them.
Yeah, like a radio show.
I guess it has its nuance to it, but it's different.
There's a big exile on her show, so, I mean, it's, you know...
You have to learn all the characters.
Yeah.
Well, there's some a lot of haters and it's like I don't know I get the banter and it's kind of like, you know
Like did I could she come white night trolls like there's good in the bed
And then there's ones that really want to fucking destroy you like they really are bothered by something that they heard about a grain of truth
It might have a piece of a truth, right?
And then it just turns into the game of telephone and that's it. You're everywhere
Yeah, yeah, you gotta you just gotta weed that shit out
But it's like, you know, it's crazy, but discord is like is the worst
I mean, I'm on I I wish I would have never ever ever ever
Got involved with that whole thing. I had no idea the rules, you know, the boundaries what eyes are looking
Are you guys on discord? No, I don't need this cause no
I'm there to crop all years back, but I just couldn't get mad round it and you end up throwing significant, you know
Yeah, I tried it and didn't vibe to it
We're gonna get a link. Yeah, it's like all the time
link link link
Yeah, but you're gonna do sit there right I'm all down or seven
I'm still my space so
That's funny good old days
So what time is it where you're at?
It's almost 3 30 here. Yeah, me too. I'm now is 20 past nine in the morning
I'm having a coming up here. Just a lively little bit. That's GBT
Who you asking me? GBT is great Britain time. Oh, wow. Oh
You're over by Manchester, right?
Yeah, not far from it. Yeah, you know that Bill Marshow?
Yeah, I don't watch it. I don't watch it either
But he has a on YouTube I was like scrolling through and he has that thingy
I don't know if it's like in a little it's got like two easy chairs and he does cocktails and he always has a guest
You know I'm talking about yeah, and he had that guy young blood. I think his name's young blood
He's like an up but he's sung for like the Ozzy after Ozzy died. Oh, that's right. Yep. Yep. Yeah. Oh, yeah, I've seen him not a golf kid
And he said something about me. I don't know
Great
Who a young blood he wasn't that great. Yeah
Yeah, he's more
Yeah, he said something about who he um after Ozzy Osbourne died
They had that concert. I don't know is MTV or something one of those award shows or something and then
Huh
Solar emo crap with him emo. Yeah. Yeah. Oh
Real emo gothic combined type fucking the world I choose
Yeah, who's like 28? I mean, I guess I don't know you you know like in another that's old or it could be old in your mind
Or it could be very young so what do you say?
so he was he was in his basement he just said they both i mean it's cool show where they can
sit down and you know you have a cocktail you smoke a cigarette or a joint i mean you're doing it
it's like you know it that's pretty cool interview style but uh he's what brought me up and thought
about it because you just said manchester and he said england and he said he lived in a little
town but nobody knew so then he just would reference to manchester because it's like within
What the hell?
I can't myself in the bathroom
Oh, baby
He'll twist your view
He'll smile when he knows he's got through to you
No, bring these guys there
Think that is steady as stone
Or he's the stars but never alone
Kind in the core, sharp as a flame
from Canada's hush to the world's loud room
he stands his ground clears the gloom
he'll question your gods defend your rights
and still wish you peace at the end of the night
You didn't put salt in the parameter hash.
Proud of you.
Yo.
Did you sleep at night or did you sleep in the morning?
No, not at the street.
Yeah, I said I'm up twenty-fourth now.
This is how many I've heard of in my cat.
Thirty-nine.
Yes, Tom.
That's a big time to buy it all.
It'll be for a panel ball in here.
You burned your cat.
Okay, my cat.
Dad's song.
Dad.
You just got a little slob.
He said that.
They did as well.
My friends do it to me.
Don't fuck that up
Give me a wave, man
You know they do it inside
Where are you wrong?
That's not why he said it
I can't put it wrong
What can you do about it, Johnny?
You can't take everyone else
Nothing, nothing, I'm fancy
So why are you mad about it?
Nothing, I got no bra on and no under and come, come, come with it, baby
Don't even have an idea
All you will want is shit on the flames
Hear that, Darryl?
I didn't even hear a shit
Yeah, no bra, no panties on.
No bra, no panties.
Yeah, walking around, he's his nails cut.
You know, he does the kneading, like making the biscuits.
All right
This again this lady. Okay. Yeah, I don't there's nothing I can do about it
But they won't leave it alone and it bothers me because how many cats you have
Right now I have one. I used to have three at one time. No, I have one, but one passed away last December and
You know, I was I was talking about it in discord and I said something about I needed to get a bit
You know how you get the what he called the vet not vaccine
Brady shot whatever it is for the leasing nowadays
You got to have like your put has to even if it's an indoor animal you have to like show records. It's like what so
right yeah dragging my feet on it and then you know i don't feel what what's going on here
i'm my eyes are closed when i was talking who's that in the back i got add and he's got me so
fuck full clemson crazed up here with this stuff it's a party it's a party but it's so late i don't
know should i go back in the fridge you know what i have what kind of beer i got i look like
I can't stand it how I talk.
With open panels that never shy away from the truth, I am Psyche, your guide through tarot, prophecy, and the unfiltered clash of voices.
Tonight, we're stepping into the panel verse where allies and trolls alike reveal themselves in every card turn.
Every word spoken is part of the story.
So stay sharp, stay curious, because once the gates open, anything can happen.
The show is about to begin. Let's go.
This is Lilith Scorpiana and you're watching Psyche Awakens TV.
Psyche Awakens TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul where truth burns through illusion
and transformation demands courage.
Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss where raw truth claws at
your core and transformation diverges all fear.
It's a relentless plunge into that only the brave emerge reborn.
Enjoy!
Enjoy.
Was I muted?
Yeah, we all get mutated in that place. Oh, I feel like so like against freedom of
Everything
I can't even see
What let's let's break bread. Just give me something to eat. We'll be good. I
Don't want to know. I love it be in okay. Well, you know what kind of beer I got
Got you remember, I don't know but you but coming up that you know how you drive the
Heineken it's like a skunk. Yeah
Yeah, I got it. I got some Heineken's in there. It's an S. It's Tony after that. Heineken's gross like nowadays
Checkerbug what nothing
Come for him motherfucker
I think it's making me dizzy the thing in the background the hands very
He's put a spell on you
Not to give words of wisdom truth, I mean I stand by that stuff
Why was David crying the other day?
Was he crying?
Yeah, you show pictures of his kids.
You show pictures of his kids.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, because,
because, you know, he gets a bad rap and he's a, you know,
people, you know, you call it like somebody a womanizer
or you're an old dude or you know, your tan
or you know, you're blah, blah, blah, he just goes.
That's why he was, he was crying because of that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, I'm leading up to the story.
He is showing that there's a time in his life, like, you know, he was just saying that, you know, you know, whatever he met is to be and he was talking about how they're parting before the wedding and then after the when the kids came, he just changed his life and he said he pulled the earring out of his ear and he straightened up and quit doing any drugs and like, you know, and he's a good father, even though the marriage didn't last and so forth.
He was reminiscing yeah absolutely good a good a good dad
You know, maybe them, you know, right
You know, I like the format that he had but he seems to get a little emotional about the fucking lowered chat
That other one on the buddies tonight
It was everything was crusty busty dickhead fuckhead the cock sucker, you know, sorry, did I say that?
It was constant but rainbowl of spew so you might like that one better so
who's the one that brought the cat into the frame who's that his wife that was him that's buddy. Oh
She has a girlfriend a girlfriend. I think a girlfriend. That's okay
Sabrina, okay. I wasn't watching too long. Yeah. Well, I was in there and I have a I had a wrench
And I never hardly go in there, but then there was a Joni, Jonika like you know because they made fun of me cuz I
Thought there was you know, that's not that wasn't me
yeah they were right they usually are because she has to spell on you but it
can't hurt me you don't offend me you don't even exist to me you
that's why I'm always worried to be nothing
This is my shot.
I mean, I'm coming here for uplifting and not kill myself, and I'm not having a good day.
What did I do to you?
Josh Tapey, the hell.
Let's see.
We are war, we represent, Bita, we represent.
We are war, we represent, we represent, we represent.
I don't know what Alex is going through.
Why Alex is going through here?
What happened?
I have no idea, she's literally fucking obsessed
and keeps dog-seeing my name and last night thinking it's funny
on like one, like, on one, like,
No, she says Carl is like crazy on the other note. He she says he's not
Like I don't know why she's even bringing Carl into this. She can just like
Go and like date him or whatever. She's a little obsessed with Carl too. I guess
She said that I would like you have like some kind of ring going on, you know
Where is KK? Can KK come up here too?
Yeah, hold on. I don't got KK Blah. I can't reach out to KK.
And I was talking to a car right there and she missed on she missed on assuming. I was talking to a car when I said
Things and she'd be like look right here. Look look
I know only that see and that's all I got to watch out to play a clip
That's how I'm very cautious with that
None of that
She got she got close to sight because of you now she want to be close to Carl because of you now
I'm thinking about it. Maybe she's trying to be close to me because I was close to you too
I'm just kidding I think she it really has it out for you and anyone that's like
associates with you then she thinks they're part of whatever but at the same
time she just needs like someone to um she's a bully you know she's like an
internet bully she likes to like make fun and laugh like a witch
She's like so like amazing, but then at the other end she'll go and do these like Bible readings like see she's like
You have really bad energy you and psyche belong together you guys are
Yikes
I didn't, I didn't, I didn't actually, I would just give up my ear because he's going to the room.
I'm like that.
This guy, all he does is bitch this guy.
Now, I mean, defend Alex when? I mean, I don't need to defend Alex.
Yeah, I always said, people fear her.
I didn't even defend yourself.
Fear, she's a regular person.
So that's what she does
She does she takes shit too far
See him on the panel
Look, he gets like fucking mad because some people like
He was just sitting there quietly saying nothing
And be like j-dog that's fucked up don't talk about that shit that's sensitive this and that he just sits there and like smiles
And like consumes it and then he cries that oh my god
A lot of people don't like me. They judge
They you know what them do fucking better and like Christine like she was on the panel
Summer has told him like several times. You know what you're playing with like crystal land is like a touchy subject
Can you stop doing it? Oh, yeah, yeah, I'm just playing and he jumped off and he started the life like doing that fucking title
Christine versus Crystal Marine white her why would do that?
I'm telling you, I think he's the other burdo on this guy
Even
No disrespect to my Mexicans here, but clumsy and in general,
two lazy ass Mexicans,
I'm never seeing lazy Mexicans in my life.
No, no, always.
Oh, listen, I'm not crying over the fucking diet.
I was like, I was doing my own panel last night.
I had like, you know.
It was like for Katie's birthday and he sent, you know, Mason over there and, um, you know,
Mason was like, I don't know why it's like he sent me over here.
And I was like, I don't know either.
And then all of a sudden a couple of people sent me a screenshot.
They're like, he's restreaming you, you know, like an art interaction with Mason.
That was like trying to explain to me, you know, there's not the best place, like, you
know, um, nothing against you.
You are a nice guy.
But yeah, so then he goes and then he comes back on my panel last time when we're playing trivia
Let him up cordially with nice to love even though I was kind of like um fucking tired
He's being fake or whatever then he goes today and starts doing his bullshit again
And I told him I was like, you know, you do this and then you like get upset like how many chances
I have to give him summer came up on this panel and she was like, yeah, you know
That's like really bothers like somebody that was a supporter of yours like Christine
Just don't play that fucking clip over and over again. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, fine. Fine. And then he doesn't give
Yeah, no respect their respect
Yeah, yeah, I can't spend them and then he runs behind people. I noticed that he don't want to talk
I don't want to talk about his little buck like I don't really care
But why you keep going with the same old shit same old shit same old shit
This motherfucker talking shit about psyche, you know, you know, yeah
I'm neither on my summer like literally I let him on my panel last night
Everything was cool and then he goes back and he just starts again with like, you know
his AI song and this bullshit and like
Oh, you know a bunch of people in your chat don't like me and I'm like, you know you have like
J-Dog and like most of the people that hate me modded. In fact, you went as far as to mod Carl,
which I don't have anything against like Carl, but I know that he was being vindictive and he
was doing it on purpose just to break me. I hear voices all day and night and talk to them about
You're right.
He buried Peter's voice and he had taken me as a detour to these voices.
Wow.
And I'm beholden to the story.
Power of the Most High, God is God.
Speaking of...
Peace out.
Oh, bye, Goddy.
Have a good night.
Yeah.
Speaking of annoying voices, how about this guy?
He's just like I can't even understand a word. He's dead. I'm sorry, Joanie. Like I was a little I'm like a little bit
Who's this? Who is it? He's right. He always still in there
How he's gonna hate me for this gonna hate he will hate me forever if I do this. He's my mod though
I mean, it's like, okay. You're just in trouble. You're in trouble mod. You're in trouble. Come back later
I'll kick him out of the studio
God guys that felt like such a read such a rush. I can't got out of the studio too
Gosh, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to show that. Oh my god. Now there I am. I can't figure it out
I did oh my god, you don't see if I don't look like that then it's probably somebody in like a mask
Especially watch if they have a beanie on or something or if they were
You kind of supports me really well, I'll fix the I'll fix this
Fix it
No, no, I'm not be it. I'm not remember wouldn't be funny if I was be there
Sorry, no, I'm in real trouble
That was not I'm just not
Doesn't mean I'm like same thing meanest me that it can't do it like her appropriate rotation
I tried though you like the music think you think it is are you like that I'm
gonna play the thing that is song and you guys don't see it here that I think
that's worth hearing a second time don't you guys agree you have to hear this I
mean this first thing that is thank you for the top sponsor of the night you're
appreciated you know what until you tell me please don't play that song again
He's a thinker from the frost and pine
Head shines bright, got a reasoned mind
He'll test your words, he'll twist your view
But he'll smile when he knows he's got through to you
Mind in the core, sharp as a flame, fair as the wind that carries his name.
From Canada's hush to the world's loud room, he stands his ground, clears the gloom.
At the end of the fight
Think that it's steady as stone
Argus the stars, but never alone
Generous heart, never cruel old
It's for the fair, stands for the true And I hope love finds its way to you
So raise a glass to the northern light To the man who argues but gives
It is a matter of what I
Never I never did anybody I know that I never hurt anybody in my life
Well, of course we all hurts people's feelings sometimes, but I never I can even fight
I'm very about personal freedom, but also responsibility. I don't know.
Get a bad rap. I'm still there. I'm still on it. I don't know. Nobody's still here. Anybody out there?
Is that is that is amber H H H H in the
Room did anybody see an amber H H H they can I can anybody summon amber H H H H to the room
We kept a Christmas fine. Got you
Charisma are you are you somebody I know? Oh my gosh, and I'm getting you why?
Chris not I need to talk to you on the on the panel, please
Because I don't want I don't want I'm about to make Godia maybe a managing moderator
Then how the power real you don't want that it's like that'd be like it's only my last resort though
I have to trust you because it's I really have trusted you, but it's like I'm so I'm so if I get my person
I most trust it turned out to be the person that was doing everything the whole time or not be surprised, right?
So you're not gonna, right? I'm always surprised in any way, but it I just like to like really resolve this
Storyline because ready to go to a new new cycle, right?
Yeah, I don't know am I explaining it right? I don't think I know what I think it was a second second
hurricane punch
but
It was like I haven't drink this much in a long time. It's only two. I only two of them Christmas mad that it's Christmas
Alexander, please. I'm Christmas Alexander. I'm gonna be very embarrassed. I always suit
Charisma like you were such a you're such a good mod
Like you know, it's like unless they were saying like, you know
Like stuff like my address or like oh, you know, we're coming to get psyche
There's like hardly any reason I didn't see any big comments like that
See like look look look. She said the way she said something amazing about me. I'll just have her
I'll stick around until she I
See screenshots guys
If you have you have something your evidence, but I don't have any evidence
That people are trying to
Prison's Apollo
my god
It's getting very very complicated
Really good. I thought she was like a Latina woman and she's like some like elderly Greek man
She was embarrassed. Hold on hold on hold on
Yeah, one more street for you guys here
You and ghosts with your halo dim
Airplane mode, I felt it in my skin
So I was sitting like designer gold
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing
Not to be solicial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you crave the chaos I fit, cause love like cars ain't never dead
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I want to curse you
I could never rise above
Don't call it rage, it's recollection
Not to be divine, but I love you
This sin was born from your reflection
We trade halos for horns, it's fair
Every wound you gave, I wear
We take turns being the villains, muse
But damn it, I still want to lose
Not to be celestial, but you made my pain perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from a stranger's lair
Just to prove that I still care, you'd fall apart
Cause you know it's true, no one sins the way I do
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I wanna curse you, I could never
You can't forget what was never spoken
Every scar, a holy mark
Every kiss, another spark
Not to be divine, but I love you
God of desire and shadows between
Cupid's wings beating against fate's cruel
One spark, one touch
To her
We don't play fair, chat blowin' up like divine confessions
True bombs drop, no time for confessions
You on logic, we bend it, drama, we mend it
Panel full of chaos, but the vibes transcendin'
If a troll wanna bark, we clap back politely
With Andromalius watchin' nightly
They swing truth like justice in the moon, like gift is subs
Yeah, the cold keeps growing, community wild, but the energy's flowing
Welcome to Psyche Awakens TV
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre, believe me?
We laugh, we scream, we read the unseen
Father Psyche, the cat daddy, king of the stream
Welcome to Psyche Awakens TV
With truth and madness, sip the same tea, it's a family
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Cards flip, candles drip, shadows in the mist
Trolls talk slick, but they cease to exist
We're half chaos, half or a cool flame
And every night's a ritual in Psyche's name
No scripts, no filters, no chilling sight
We stream raw truth till the morning light
So grab your tea, grab your mic
This ain't YouTube, this is an underworlds talk show
You are now initiated
Father Psyche is spoken
Spoken
the night you light up the air a spark in the silence so be i
We were with Tony, yeah, I swore it was true.
You laughed it off, said, psyche, I'm just me, not that dude.
You're ready to crash out when the moment feels right.
Top donate or energy, you light up the night.
Big brother in the chat with that wild grin.
Every time you roll in, the fun begins.
Thank you, ghost, I won't forget you.
till my face turns blue your funny as hell yeah it's always a blast these
moments we're making are built to last thank you ghost you're one of a kind
with your big heart and mischief and your quick fire mind
you cracked the whole panel you keep it alive dropping jokes in the
Got that big bro style got that easy sway if I had to choose you'd be here in
Quick, firemind.
From the late night chaos to the morning light.
You've been here holding it down just right.
If there's a hall of fame for the real and true.
I'd carve your name in gold ghost.
That's you.
Listen, are you Tony?
No.
You're just telling me you're wrong.
No, Sucky, I'm not.
I don't care anymore, Mesa.
I don't care anymore for Tony.
Not Tony, huh?
No, it's just me, Sucky.
I'm me.
Maybe.
I believe you, baby.
You know what?
Tony's not a bad name.
I had a relative named Tony.
No, Sucky, you know my name is Mesa.
I can't be Tony if my name's Mesa.
What if your name is Tony Mason, I
Don't know it could be though
If your name was Tony Mason, then you'd have both the names and so yeah, it would be correct actually
Yeah, it could be that though psyche, but I don't know I think I don't
Because I don't want to think too hard about it. My head's already hurting a little bit just even so I can guess who was on live earlier
You know Queen Natalie
Oh, yeah, she's awesome Jesus. You know Queen Natalie once put her let her leg all the way
All over her than her head she can lift her foot higher than her head
I never saw that though. So I know if they ask her sometime, but just don't call her 10 times on Facebook
She
Saki she was she was just live a little bit while ago, but like when you were I think you're I think you were still alive
It's tough. Yeah, I don't know if I was live or dead, but
Probably dead. I'm if you know, I mean like live. No, it's like, you know what I mean like live like on here on your channel
No, I know, but I'm alive too. I mean, I have
Yeah, our nearest thing that is this Tony and
Okay, guys, I
I mean if I was like, you know
Trying to play a clue and I like had like, you know much much more drugs
So sucky sucky. She says she had to go though. Just a little like a little while ago
She says she had to go take a shower, but you me went on there though. Did you know you me went out on there?
Who's taking a shower?
So Queen Natalie, but you me I think you I think your friend you me was on her channel though
It's like, you know who's you me is our in the shower
Yeah, oh my god
No, it's not. No, it's like, it's not what you think. It's not what they're doing. They're
having dirty and lesbian things. No, it's like they were just talking on the same panel
though. You mean clean Natalie was in panel. Yeah, it's the same, the same anal.
So it's like they were both on the same, uh, you know, now it makes sense it makes much more sense
But but the thing was like she actually said that's her first time on Queen Natalie's channel, that's what you me said
You me said that
Yeah, that's what you me said. Yeah, do you call her a liar?
No
Why not
Because I've never seen her on there before so I think she's right
Okay
Anyway
So you're one of a kind
Like you're one of a kind
Hey
You're just playing that song psych. Yeah, hey
Ghost you're one of a kind with your quick flyer mower and you're filled by the mind
Oh my gosh, I'm holding a thing out right now
It's like you're one of a kind
Maybe the world is blind or just a little unkind
Is that song is that song dedicated to just ghosts though or is that to you too?
Well that one the way I play was for ghosts. I mean, it's like Mason once you donate like about a thousand dollars. I'll make you a song too
So what do I got do I have to pay for it? Yeah, you take your whatever when you you're gonna get your disability check
And then you take you just
Sign it all over to me, and then I'll make the decisions from now on but how do you mean the money I get from the government site
No, no, no, no, no, I'm just it was a suit. It was that was the worst joke I ever said in my life
I would that was it was like it didn't make any sense. That's so dumb
So I could tell my government money to my gift
Anything like that. I didn't say anything. Stop saying something like using me things stop it
Stop it now
It was a joke. It's called satire
You're just joking with me the whole time. So you hold the whole time the entire time
How many are joking to me about that
course
Wait, you think I was me serious?
No, I don't know so I guess sometimes people get money from the government. It's true. There's people that do do that
Man, that's good, but I know I don't anybody from there. Oh, oh, we have a guest music. Do you want to talk to me? I guess
Yeah
Sorry, that's the one that's the one of a kind. That's so
If you'd like that song, you know, you can definitely feel like it's yours to you
Hold on Iron Man awakens the drummer. Does anybody know who Iron Man awakens the drummers?
I'm not sure I can trust that person. I've never heard that day in my life
Anybody know Iron Man awakens the drummer?
Because I've never heard of such thing though. Yeah, I mean I heard of I've heard of the drummer and I've heard of the awakens
And I've heard of Iron Man. Yeah, I've heard of all those things but not together though
So like you know what you get corn bomber
Or
Get somebody it's just crazy enough to take
Don't you make them turn their camera when they're backstage on huh, let me see
Who is that show me who you are? Oh?
It's a real person. Hold on
It looks like a they look attractive actually
Psych like who is it man? Who is it? I don't know
Awakens the drama
That good times I kind of it kind of looks like good times. Is that you know that it's good times are on reason I
Don't I can't tell it's hard to tell
I
Like that does he or Naz or I'm sorry does that sound good to you like what's going on like you like what he's doing
Basically, this is your brother. Thank you for introducing us
Too slow
So I guess another it's another drummer so that's who it is
Are you that was the one from the Indians days?
Tell you what I don't know who you're but he sounds like and I don't mean to be rude here because you know
I'm always trying to be nice, but yeah, you're gonna have to stick to singing to the AI brother because iron man
Let me tell you something I
Am AI
Go see turn into AI man
I am AI. I have an AI for you and you end up in Iowa. I won't show you my you know, you never know
You need to get yellow gloves man and make the whole ensemble work better
Oh, my gloves. I've got them over here. Shit. No shit. I spoke to you saying processing gloves. Thank you for the instastance
Damn you should have came here
Processed love was behind me
Glove has been processed
Thank you. Process complete.
So it gets weapons activated.
I'm feeling funky.
We're having a dance off now.
Oh, shit.
I am going to go snow it's no ghost this weapons activated man. That's what he said. He said act weapons activated. I
Don't know what the fuck that means
That's something you have to take up with him ghost ask him emails I'm trying to talk to him, but he won't answer
Is that
I love you
You can't say that's all trim man. Is that with a man?
Yay, hi, no, no, I don't man
I love you. You make head
Oh, mr. Ghost. I want to do iron things with you
Is that I had a man? I had a man. Yeah
Who is that with my iron with you?
I don't know. Is that? Is that
you need a healthy diet of iron
in your diet? That's where I
come in. Oh, is that you? You
need your diet. So, that's why
you're the iron man. We get it.
I
Am I there's a break
Thing goes like a total before he says what he says weapons activated
I mean, I thought you were gonna do like a 30 second stick
Oh shit
Put the fire on
Come on get
May the sun
Startin' game
Oh shit
What is that fucking stem at?
Can you find the stem?
Thank you
Okay, where's the poker?
I'll hand it
You mean that! Target activated!
Hmm? Why me?
What the hell is he doing there?
I don't know.
I'll go speak to Ty. I'll go speak to him.
You have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it, you have to get used to it
Well, you have to keep an eye on Ericko.
When you wake up...
You know, I'm not trying to be mean, but...
I'm not trying to be mean, but...
It's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not, it's not
That is me!
Me too! I know, me too!
It's a Broly calling you!
It's a Broly calling you! The pump's starting!
Oh, I get it, man!
Target activated!
I think it's 4.8. I think we fucked up.
4.5!
No, she just wants us to welcome him up. He wants us to welcome him in because he's with us now
I'm very new my iron tarts are they're not rusted yet, but they're very new
What'd you do
I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target. I have to acquire a target
Oh
Shit, what's going on here?
You guys you guys
Who's that? You? Mr. Saiki? You and me? Miss?
You and me?
That wasn't the best.
What the hell was that?
Was that in the bowl?
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, hell.
I need to be the dog dick for this.
That would be shit.
Uh-oh.
What?
What happened?
Don't
Visions made flesh, I declare it now.
Autumn leaves and the gavel fall.
Through death and dawn, I will guide them all.
Rebel stars in the tribal flame.
Dreams cross borders, none stay the same.
On the other hand, I was right.
Oh, now I want to go to sleep.
Thank you.
When I take my shirt off, but I'm in backstage. I got all this shit on I could be just a
Fucking joshmo. Nobody give a fuck
Take my shirt off
Fuck that's like
I'm out of peace in me
Uh-oh Charlize she's got her first victim corner
She doesn't have to do it, but she wants to do it.
I played Charlie's stare one time in a Sonic restroom over here.
Had the family knocking on the door.
It was on the Instagram. I think it got taken down because of how bolder.
My Instagram was
I think I drank from a
Windex one time when I put in that was
Arnold Schwarzenegger's
baby mama's living
We shouldn't be
Daydream. Damn it.
Good to the kids. Use blue power, right?
Don't use the real thing.
Got wind bags.
Got some lingering effects I find out.
What were we talking about?
I needed some water.
No, no.
여기가 워낙
Acquiring Target
I always wanted to work at Abu Khabib and Fik.
From birth the night was wild, the cards were true
and then we worked out for our lives.
Yeah!
This is your brain after two switch weeks
Welcome to the panel, need your shame at the door
One more drink and someone's on the door
Love to lose your trust in cloud
It's a gentle madhouse, scream it out loud
still beams. There's a light through the chaos, a vibe so true, that's all because of every
single one of you.
Pizza, my sweetheart, Persian Queen delight, with your laugh so loud, you light up the night.
Page with the heart and the jokes that land, blonde bombshell with a beer in hand.
We laugh, we read, and we climb to the top
So thank you for the chats, the laughs, the love
For the super chats raining like stars above
To the members, the mods, my wild family
You're the heartbeat of this cosmic symphony
It gets crazy, but we never stop together
up the flame.